<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Radius]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Radius]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/radius/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 23:35:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/radius/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Something More Original Than Sin!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Evangelical believers are famous for seeking to share our faith in Jesus by leading with the message that "our sins have separated us from God." There are certainly some passages in the Bible that, as isolated verses, make such a case from a certain angle. The ironic problem is that most believers, after coming to faith and connecting with God more personally, begin to see very clearly how God was working in their lives before they came to "saving" faith. Indeed, the fact that God was always "nearby us" and exercising His grace toward us are keys to properly understanding our life story and bringing healing to our broken hearts. Immanuel has always been nearby us - oftentimes offering us help in ways we didn't necessarily perceive and sometimes intervening to protect and preserve us. As Paul informed the philosophers of Athens -</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radius/something-more-original-than-sin/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fa18cc7f-caa9-41db-b170-b452e73b8f5e</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 19:15:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Michael's Blog: Recapture the Wonder]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>He who did not spare his own Son but gave him up for us all, how will he not also with him graciously give us all things? (Romans 8:32 ESV) A whole bloc of theological teaching through the centuries has basically promoted something quite contrary to the above revolutionary verse. This popular thinking basically leaves us with this powerful impression: "Because the Father sent Jesus to die on the cross to forgive us for our sins and take us to heaven if and/or when we die, we really don't need anything else...nor should we rightly expect anything else...from Him." Have you ever gotten this impression in the past as I have?</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radius/michaels-blog-recapture-the-wonder/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">48c82dbe-6ca7-4f4c-8c40-e0e7a1ee272d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 19:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Our Family Christmas 2014]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Our Family Christmas 2014</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9b500822f9c1416bdf3065cbaf3d8b9d07fd1f7e.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>urn:uuid:52391570-8766-4b4e-9459-1bd8feb8a5ab</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">01151202-1e9d-49e1-9647-b77a34a75a2a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 20:43:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>